http://www.lifesolutionsplus.com/privacy-statement-i-3.html

Privacy Statement
This privacy statement explains our privacy practices for our customers who register to use our Web site, LifeSolutionsPlus.com, for delivery of products to a U.S. address.We respect your right to privacy.  Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us.  This privacy statement explains our policy regarding the collection, use disclosure and protection of personal information.  The terms of this privacy statement apply to information collected from you, unless different terms are specified as part of a special offer, or in another form or contract we provide you and you consent to those terms by participation in the special offer or the program, or otherwise.Information Collection & UseLog In/RegistrationIn order to purchase items from this Web site, you must first create an account by adding your email address and personal password.  By creating an account at LifeSolutionsPlus, Inc., you will be able to shop faster, be up to date on an order's status, and keep track of the orders you have previously made.  During registration you are required to give contact information such as name and email information.  We use this information to contact you to answer any questions or supply information about the products or services on our site.LifeSolutionsPlus, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on http://www.lifesolutionsplus.com/.  LifeSolutionsPlus, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.OrdersIf you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information such as name, shipping address, phone number and email address. You must also provide financial information such as credit card number, expiration date, validation code and billing/credit card address.  We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.All customer credit card information is kept strictly confidential.  At times, shipping information is shared with other companies for the purpose of drop shipping items that our company does not keep in stock or are out of stock at the time when the order is placed.  This is done to expedite the order to the customer.  No information is ever sold to other companies for any purpose.Customer ServiceBased upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the service you request, advise you of shipment, and to manage your account.  We will communicate with you by email or telephone only in accordance with your wishes.If you wish to subscribe to any newsletters offered on our website, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.SecurityThe security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our order form, we encrypt that information using an SSL which is short for Secure Sockets Layer. The SSL protocol was developed by Netscape and is supported by all popular web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Netscape, AOL and Opera.  We follow the generally accepted industry standard to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. However, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  If you have any questions or concerns about security on our website, you can send an email to us at sales@lifesolutionsplus.com.Changes in this Privacy StatementIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our home page.Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at sales@lifesolutionsplus.com .
Categories
ClearanceHousehold AidsSignature LifeSpeciality EquipmentBathroom Aids-> Compression SocksDiabetic AccessoriesDressing AidsHerbal PacksIncontinence AidsKitchen AidsMagnifiersMedicine OrganizersMobility Aids-> Pet ProductsRecreationSupport Pillows / BackrestsOrthopedicsWriting AidsCaregivers CornerNeck and Back Pain ReliefRehab and Therapy
Information
Terms and ConditionsOrdering and Shipping InformationPrivacy StatementAbout UsShop Online with ConfidenceHours of OperationProduct Catalogs, Brochures, Flyers and Instructions Sitemap LinksContact Us
Featured Products
Flexible Desk Type Magnifier $34.95
Search
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Summer Sale Items
Now Available: New PDF Catalogs.Download a full catalog, or select categories and create your own!
Best Sellers
01.Good Grips Button Hook02.No Rinse Shampoo Cap03.Good Grips Utensils04.Key Turner05.Lotion Applicator06.TheraBand Hand Exerciser07.No Rinse Bathing Wipes08.Comfort Cool Arthritis Thumb Splint Black09.Good Grips Weighted Utensils10.The Original BED BUDDY Hot and Cold Pack
Customer Reviews
Works very well considering having lost use of right arm & h ..
Shoppers Now Online
There currently are 5 guests online.
Articles
New Articles (0)All Articles (22)Activities of Daily Living (6)Care Givers (3)Health Maintenance (5)Nutrition (3)Occupational Health (1)Vision Care (1)Arthritis (3)
Store Feeds
Stay up to date on assistive technology and independent living products using our RSS FeedsBrowse to a specific category to narrow the feed selectionProducts Reviews  Articles  Topics  Product  Category
Home
Your Cart
Log In
Checkout
Contact Us
Blog
Please SelectClearanceHousehold AidsSignature LifeSpeciality EquipmentBathroom Aids  Bathroom Grab Bars  Raised Toilet Seats/Commodes  Shower Chairs and BenchesCompression SocksDiabetic AccessoriesDressing AidsHerbal PacksIncontinence AidsKitchen AidsMagnifiersMedicine OrganizersMobility Aids  Lift Chairs  Power Mobility  Walkers and Rollators  Wheelchairs  Canes and CrutchesPet ProductsRecreationSupport Pillows / BackrestsOrthopedicsWriting AidsCaregivers CornerNeck and Back Pain ReliefRehab and Therapysubmit
